adguk-blog.com 2014-12-01

# Privacy Policy ~ ADG (UK) Blog

**What information do we collect?**  

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.   
  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site.   
  
These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you.   
  
These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.   
  
To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**What do we use your information for?**   
  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:   
  
**To improve our website:**  
**  
** We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.  
  
**Do we use cookies?**   
  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.  
  
**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**   
  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.   
  
This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.   
  
We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.   
  
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.  
  
**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**   
  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.  
  
**Online Privacy Policy Only**   
  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.  
  
**Your Consent**   
  
By using our site, you consent to our [websites privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).  
  
**Changes to our Privacy Policy**   
  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.   
  
**Contacting Us**   
  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
